# **Benjamin Paris**

Ben is a resourceful engineer with a diverse background in web development, embedded device operations, and team leadership. Effectively combining technical expertise with strong communication and problem-solving skills to deliver high quality results. A lifetime learner with a focus on cybersecurity.

San Diego, CA 92117
(206) 437-5244
benjaminparis@proton.me
linkedin.com/in/benpariswork
github.com/benpariswork

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Seattle Yacht Media, Remote — Web Systems Engineer

November 2022 - PRESENT

- Created and deployed customer facing website with responsive web design using Vue 3 and AWS.
- Continuously developing pages and UX in order to fully demonstrate the company's expertise.
- Optimized deployments using AWS Amplify and bunny.net to provide content delivery and image transformation.

# **Meta (via Q Analysts),** Redmond WA — Embedded Device Technician

January 2022 - August 2022

- Provisioned embedded AR/VR devices using Linux CLI, Windows CLI, shell scripting (bash and powershell), and Python 3.
- Conducted risk analysis and mitigation for workflows used throughout device operations.
- Unblocked tickets by providing troubleshooting for a variety of SAAS suites.

## **Amazon**, Seattle WA — Bullpen Hero

June 2021 - March 2022

- Directed an adaptive team with 2-6 essential workers for 40+ hours/week.
- Lead warehouse communication with third party (B2B) drivers.
- Utilized a variety of internal tools to ensure the accuracy of thousands of items going to customers.

### **EDUCATION**

# **University of Oregon**, Remote — *Certificate*

October 2020 - April 2021

Learned foundational cybersecurity concepts and frameworks. Gained hands-on experience with a variety of industry tools and systems.

#### **SKILLS**

- Leadership
- Communication
- Cybersecurity
- Engineering
- Troubleshooting
- Optimization
- Bash Scripting
- AWS
- DNS
- CDN (bunny.net)
- Vue JS
- Javascript/HTML/CSS

#### Certifications

CompTIA Security+

Code: C43J467QE144145B

Verify at:

http://verify.CompTIA.org